[
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter january march april",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "united states agency",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "united states",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "chemonics international inc global health supply chain",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "washington",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "chemonics international inc chemonics",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "anthony savelli",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "arlington va p",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "thirdparty logistics pl fourthparty logistics act",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "cor",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "fda us food drug administration fmis financial management information system",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "fiscal year",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "iso international organization standards",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "kuehnenagel kpi key performance",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "llin long",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "rdt",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "united nations",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "united parcel service",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "us",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "three",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "three",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter january march first quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "sayana",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "december",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "january",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "first quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "two day",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "first quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "first",
        "ORDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "four",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "first quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "united parcel",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "africa",
        "LOC"
    ],
    [
        "singapore",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "netherlands",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "rdc",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "three",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "kuehnenagels",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "fourth",
        "ORDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "first",
        "ORDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "four",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "fiscal year",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter percent",
        "PERCENT"
    ],
    [
        "ninety three",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "first",
        "ORDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "two",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "next quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "march",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "monthly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "weekly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "cor",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "next quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "two",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "first",
        "ORDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "two",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "february",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "geneva",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "march",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "weekly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "third week april",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "months",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "september",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "botswana burma",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "ethiopia",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "ghana",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "haiti",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "malawi mozambique",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "namibia",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "rwanda",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "vietnam",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "zambia zimbabwe",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "february",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "rdc direct",
        "PRODUCT"
    ],
    [
        "february",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "generic arvs",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "march",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "march",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "one",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "weekly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "multimonth",
        "ORDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "two",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "february",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "weekly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "first",
        "ORDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "monthly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "april",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "mali uganda mali",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "february",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "february",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "ida psi kn",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "ida psi",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "next quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "months",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "ghana",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "liberia",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "malawi",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "rwanda",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "zambia zimbabwe",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "monthly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "oct march",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "commodity council reproductive health pharmaceuticals commodity council",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "three",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "netherlands",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "next quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "sayana",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "two",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "fiscal year",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "february",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "sayana",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "sayana press order ghscpsm drafted rfq sayana",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "fda",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "weekly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "weekly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "months",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "ethiopia",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "ghana",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "haiti",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "liberia",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "malawi",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "pakistan",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "rwanda",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "early quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "sayana",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "million",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "early next quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "first",
        "ORDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "weekly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "five",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "january",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "six eight",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "commodity councils mentioned",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "six eight",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "six",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "two",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "two",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "ghscqa",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "tos mou",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "four",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "months",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "weekly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "six",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "singapore",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "netherlands",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "fourth",
        "ORDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "singapore",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "netherlands",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "next quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "ida psi",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "four",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "three",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "two",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "chemonics financial management information system",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "two",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "weekly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "arrival burma",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "ghana mark morris",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "grace adeya systems",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "malawi shane mcgee",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "mozambique doris",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "mary lyn fieldnguer",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "lesotho brian",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "washington",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "june july",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "first",
        "ORDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "late quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "december",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "first",
        "ORDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "two weeks",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "july",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "burma",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "ghana",
        "GPE"
    ],
    [
        "malawi",
        "PERSON"
    ],
    [
        "zimbabwe quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "early quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "annual",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "first",
        "ORDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "march seven",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "early quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "second",
        "ORDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "first",
        "ORDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "june",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "september",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "february",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "first quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "first",
        "ORDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "external audience international association public health logisticians iaphl",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "monthly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "first quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarter",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "january",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "early january",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "united",
        "ORG"
    ],
    [
        "nine months",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "april",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "two",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "january",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "nine month",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "july",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "january",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "two",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "one",
        "CARDINAL"
    ],
    [
        "quarterly",
        "DATE"
    ],
    [
        "year quarter",
        "DATE"
    ]
]